[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It has been reported that in the period 1992-2008, Ringling Bros. and Barnum  Bailey Circus had at least this many elephant deaths caused by abuse and neglect.", "correct_answer": "24", "incorrect_answers": ["0", "1", "7"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The leaves of which of these plants are most often used for the preparation of the popular Arab dish dolma, also known as sarma?", "correct_answer": "Grape vine", "incorrect_answers": ["Palm tree", "Fig tree", "Lettuce"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1952, this Republican Senator was awarded the Distinguished Flying Cross, for his service as an aerial photographer and tail gunner during World War II.", "correct_answer": "Joseph McCarthy", "incorrect_answers": ["Lyndon Johnson", "Robert Taft", "James Watson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why does Blade team up with the Bloodpack in Blade II?", "correct_answer": "To help the Shadow Council", "incorrect_answers": ["To find his mother", "To find a cure to turn him into a mortal", "To find Whistler"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Dog Day Afternoon, the manager of the bank apologised to his girls. Why did he do this?", "correct_answer": "Because he swore", "incorrect_answers": ["Because he told them off for smoking in the bank", "Because he couldnt disarm Sonny", "Because he was unable to call the police"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pigeons were so valuable in wartime that some won medals for their service.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the fruit of the coffee plant called?", "correct_answer": "Cherry", "incorrect_answers": ["Bean", "Bead", "Clove"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many of the basic mathematical operations are needed to have an algebra?", "correct_answer": "3", "incorrect_answers": ["2", "0", "4"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year did the  great movie A Few Good Men first hit the theatres?", "correct_answer": "1992", "incorrect_answers": ["1990", "1991", "1994"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Stella Adler was the first and only American-born actor to be trained by this great acting teacher.", "correct_answer": "Konstantin Stanislavski", "incorrect_answers": ["Fritz Lang", "Sergei Eisenstein", "Sir Robert Exeter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long is the average lifespan of an elephant?", "correct_answer": "70 years", "incorrect_answers": ["15 years", "110 years", "35 years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "U.S. antitrust lawyers took Microsoft to court claiming that the company tried to use its monopolistic power to destroy this computer language.", "correct_answer": "JAVA", "incorrect_answers": ["LINUS", "LOTUS", "COBOL"]}]